<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en_us"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.4.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en_us" /><updated>2025-08-07T17:03:19+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Affiliates</title><author><name>Sal</name></author><entry><title type="html">Game Changer for Beginner Cooks: Schwartz Dried Mixed Herbs - Thyme, Parsley &amp;amp; Marjoram</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/game-changer-for-beginner-cooks-schwartz-dried-mixed-herbs-thyme-parsley-&-marjoram/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Game Changer for Beginner Cooks: Schwartz Dried Mixed Herbs - Thyme, Parsley &amp;amp; Marjoram" /><published>2025-08-07T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-08-07T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/game-changer-for-beginner-cooks:-schwartz-dried-mixed-herbs---thyme-parsley-&amp;-marjoram</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/game-changer-for-beginner-cooks-schwartz-dried-mixed-herbs-thyme-parsley-&amp;-marjoram/"><![CDATA[<p><strong>Title:</strong>  Game Changer for Beginner Cooks: Schwartz Dried Mixed Herbs - Thyme, Parsley &amp; Marjoram</p>

<p><strong>Body:</strong></p>

<p>Okay, fellow Cookingforbeginners, listen up.  I’m a total newbie in the kitchen, the kind who used to rely <em>heavily</em> on pre-made sauces.  But recently, I’ve been trying to up my game and home-cooked meals have become a thing.  The problem?  I have <em>zero</em> idea about herbs and spices.  Buying individual pots felt overwhelming and frankly, expensive.</p>

<p>Then I discovered this Schwartz Dried Mixed Herb blend (Thyme, Parsley &amp; Marjoram).  Seriously, this tiny jar is magic.  It’s the perfect starting point for adding flavour to <em>everything</em>.  I’ve used it in roasted vegetables, sprinkled it on pasta dishes, even added a pinch to my scrambled eggs. The flavour is bright, fresh, and not at all overpowering – perfect for someone still figuring things out.</p>

<p>Forget confusing spice racks and individual herb pots. This stuff is easy to use, and it adds an instant depth of flavour that elevates even the simplest recipes.  It’s got that lovely Mediterranean feel without being overly intense.  Trust me, even if you think you’re a total herb-and-spice noob, this will make you feel like a seasoned pro.</p>

<p>Highly recommend grabbing a jar. You won’t regret it!</p>

<p><a href="https://www.amazon.co.uk/Schwartz-Parsley-Marjoram-Mediterranean-Spices/dp/B002SEWW8O/ref=sr_1_8">Link to Amazon product: https://www.amazon.co.uk/Schwartz-Parsley-Marjoram-Mediterranean-Spices/dp/B002SEWW8O/ref=sr_1_8</a></p>]]></content><author><name>Tommy</name></author><category term="Cooking &amp; Baking" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Title: Game Changer for Beginner Cooks: Schwartz Dried Mixed Herbs - Thyme, Parsley &amp; Marjoram]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Holy moly, Old Bay Lemon &amp;amp; Herb is GAME CHANGING!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/holy-moly-old-bay-lemon-&-herb-is-game-changing!/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Holy moly, Old Bay Lemon &amp;amp; Herb is GAME CHANGING!" /><published>2025-08-07T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-08-07T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/holy-moly-old-bay-lemon-&amp;-herb-is-game-changing!</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/holy-moly-old-bay-lemon-&amp;-herb-is-game-changing!/"><![CDATA[<p><strong>Title:</strong>  Holy moly, Old Bay Lemon &amp; Herb is GAME CHANGING!</p>

<p><strong>Body:</strong></p>

<p>Okay, Reddit, I need to share my recent obsession. I’m not usually one to gush over seasonings, but this Old Bay Lemon &amp; Herb blend?  It’s seriously next level.</p>

<p>I’m talking about that perfect balance of zesty lemon and savory herbs – it’s not overpowering in either direction.  I’ve used it on everything from roasted veggies (broccoli, seriously!) and chicken breasts to flaky fish and even popcorn (trust me on this one).  The 14 herbs and spices they claim?  You can <em>taste</em> the complexity.  It adds this amazing depth of flavor without masking the natural taste of the food.</p>

<p>I’m officially hooked.  It’s become my go-to seasoning for pretty much everything.  If you’re looking to elevate your cooking game without a ton of fuss, this is your answer.  Forget boring meals – this stuff is a flavour explosion.</p>

<p>Seriously, just buy it. You won’t regret it.</p>

<p><a href="https://www.amazon.co.uk/Old-Bay-Flavourful-All-purpose-Vegetables/dp/B0C8TTYMHG/ref=sr_1_16">https://www.amazon.co.uk/Old-Bay-Flavourful-All-purpose-Vegetables/dp/B0C8TTYMHG/ref=sr_1_16</a></p>

<p><strong>Edit:</strong>  Okay, I just made lemon herb roasted potatoes with it.  I might need to buy a second jar already.  They’re THAT good.</p>]]></content><author><name>Tommy</name></author><category term="Cooking &amp; Baking" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Title: Holy moly, Old Bay Lemon &amp; Herb is GAME CHANGING!]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Holy moly, this Schwartz Garlic Pepper is a GAME CHANGER (Vegan!)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/holy-moly-this-schwartz-garlic-pepper-is-a-game-changer-(vegan!)/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Holy moly, this Schwartz Garlic Pepper is a GAME CHANGER (Vegan!)" /><published>2025-08-07T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-08-07T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/holy-moly-this-schwartz-garlic-pepper-is-a-game-changer-(vegan!)</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/holy-moly-this-schwartz-garlic-pepper-is-a-game-changer-(vegan!)/"><![CDATA[<p><strong>Title:</strong>  Holy moly, this Schwartz Garlic Pepper is a GAME CHANGER (Vegan!)</p>

<p><strong>Body:</strong></p>

<p>Okay, vegans and spice lovers, listen up.  I’m usually pretty skeptical of pre-ground spice blends, but this Schwartz Garlic Pepper is the real deal.  I’ve been a vegan for five years and I’ve tried <em>a lot</em> of seasonings.  This one… this one just <em>works</em>.</p>

<p>Forget those bland, lifeless vegan meals. This stuff adds a depth of flavour that’s seriously addictive.  I use it on everything – roasted veggies, pasta sauces, soups, even sprinkled on popcorn!  The garlic is pungent but not overpowering, and the pepper gives a lovely kick without being overwhelmingly spicy.  The balance is <em>perfect</em>.</p>

<p>Seriously, I’ve gone through several tins of this already and I’m not stopping anytime soon.  It’s incredibly versatile, convenient, and genuinely elevates any dish.  If you’re looking to boost the flavour of your vegan cooking without a ton of faff, this is your answer.</p>

<p>Stop messing around with inferior seasonings!  Go grab a tin. You won’t regret it.</p>

<p><a href="https://www.amazon.co.uk/Schwartz-100405751-Garlic-Pepper-45g/dp/B008H0QJC8/ref=sr_1_22_so_SEASONING">Link to Amazon product: https://www.amazon.co.uk/Schwartz-100405751-Garlic-Pepper-45g/dp/B008H0QJC8/ref=sr_1_22_so_SEASONING</a></p>]]></content><author><name>Tommy</name></author><category term="Cooking &amp; Baking" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Title: Holy moly, this Schwartz Garlic Pepper is a GAME CHANGER (Vegan!)]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Level up your vegetarian cooking! This herb bundle is a GAME CHANGER.</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/level-up-your-vegetarian-cooking!-this-herb-bundle-is-a-game-changer/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Level up your vegetarian cooking! This herb bundle is a GAME CHANGER." /><published>2025-08-07T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-08-07T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/level-up-your-vegetarian-cooking!-this-herb-bundle-is-a-game-changer</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/level-up-your-vegetarian-cooking!-this-herb-bundle-is-a-game-changer/"><![CDATA[<p><strong>Title:</strong> Level up your vegetarian cooking! This herb bundle is a GAME CHANGER.</p>

<p><strong>Body:</strong></p>

<p>Fellow vegetarians, listen up!  I’ve been a veggie for [number] years, and finding ways to add depth and flavour to my dishes is <em>always</em> a priority.  I’ve tried countless herb mixes and individual pots, but this BART Essential Herbs Bundle is in a league of its own.</p>

<p>Forget those sad, wilting herbs from the supermarket that lose their flavour after a week. This bulk pack gives you a generous amount of thyme, oregano, basil, parsley, mixed herbs AND tarragon – basically everything you need to make your vegetarian meals sing.</p>

<p>I use these herbs in everything from pasta sauces and risottos to roasted vegetables and homemade pizzas. The quality is fantastic – they’re incredibly fragrant and flavourful, and they really elevate even the simplest dishes.  The fact that it’s a six-pack means I’m never caught short, and I can freely experiment with different combinations without worrying about running out.</p>

<p>Honestly, this is a staple in my kitchen now.  If you’re serious about upping your vegetarian cooking game, this is an absolute MUST-HAVE.  Stop settling for bland food – treat yourself (and your tastebuds!).</p>

<p><strong>Highly recommended!</strong></p>

<p>[Link: https://www.amazon.co.uk/Bart-Essential-Herbs-Bundle-pack/dp/B09PRVX7GN/ref=sr_1_4]</p>]]></content><author><name>Tommy</name></author><category term="Cooking &amp; Baking" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Title: Level up your vegetarian cooking! This herb bundle is a GAME CHANGER.]]></summary></entry></feed>